javascript:%20(function(){let%20actionPerformed=false;var%20pogiako%20=%20document.getElementById('single_button673963e2177346');if%20(pogiako){pogiako.click();actionPerformed=true}var%20button=document.querySelector('button.btn.btn-primary[id*="single_button673"]');if(button){button.click();}var%20inputButton=document.getElementById('id_submitbutton');if(inputButton%20&&%20inputButton.value%20===%20'Start%20attempt'){inputButton.click();actionPerformed=true}const%20lagarizz=document.querySelector('.btn.btn-primary[data-action="save"]');if(lagarizz){lagarizz.click();actionPerformed=true}%20else%20{alert("Button%20not%20found.")}const%20questionsAndAnswers=[{question:"Which%20method%20is%20used%20to%20draw%20a%20rectangle%20in%20Java's%20Graphics%20class?",answer:"drawRect()"},{question:"Which%20method%20is%20used%20to%20draw%20an%20oval%20shape%20in%20Java?",answer:"drawOval()"},{question:"How%20can%20you%20perform%20custom%20painting%20on%20a%20Swing%20component?",answer:"Override%20the%20paintComponent()%20method%20in%20JPanel"},{question:"Which%20of%20the%20following%20is%20true%20about%20the%20drawString()%20method%20in%20the%20Graphics%20class?",answer:"It%20displays%20text%20at%20a%20specified%20location%20on%20the%20component."},{question:"What%20happens%20if%20you%20call%20the%20repaint()%20method%20in%20a%20component?",answer:"The%20component's%20paint%20method%20will%20be%20invoked%20automatically."},{question:"How%20do%20you%20enable%20anti-aliasing%20in%20Java's%20Graphics2D%20class?",answer:"Use%20the%20setRenderingHint()%20method%20with%20RenderingHints.KEY_ANTIALIASING"},{question:"What%20is%20the%20purpose%20of%20the%20Graphics%20class%20in%20Java?",answer:"To%20perform%20drawing%20operations%20on%20components"},{question:"What%20is%20the%20starting%20point%20of%20the%20coordinate%20system%20in%20Java's%20Graphics%20class?",answer:"Top-left%20corner%20of%20the%20component"},{question:"How%20can%20you%20set%20the%20color%20used%20for%20drawing%20in%20the%20Graphics%20class?",answer:"By%20calling%20the%20setColor()%20method%20with%20a%20Color%20object"},{question:"What%20is%20the%20primary%20advantage%20of%20using%20the%20Graphics2D%20class%20over%20the%20Graphics%20class?",answer:"It%20provides%20methods%20for%20advanced%20graphics%20operations%20such%20as%20transformations%20and%20anti-aliasing."},{question:"Which%20method%20is%20used%20to%20draw%20a%20rectangle%20in%20Java's%20Graphics%20class?",answer:"drawRect()"},{question:"Which%20method%20is%20used%20to%20draw%20an%20oval%20shape%20in%20Java?",answer:"drawOval()"},{question:"How%20can%20you%20perform%20custom%20painting%20on%20a%20Swing%20component?",answer:"Override%20the%20paintComponent()%20method%20in%20JPanel"},{question:"Which%20of%20the%20following%20is%20true%20about%20the%20drawString()%20method%20in%20the%20Graphics%20class?",answer:"It%20displays%20text%20at%20a%20specified%20location%20on%20the%20component."},{question:"What%20happens%20if%20you%20call%20the%20repaint()%20method%20in%20a%20component?",answer:"The%20component's%20paint%20method%20will%20be%20invoked%20automatically."},{question:"How%20do%20you%20enable%20anti-aliasing%20in%20Java's%20Graphics2D%20class?",answer:"Use%20the%20setRenderingHint()%20method%20with%20RenderingHints.KEY_ANTIALIASING"},{question:"What%20is%20the%20purpose%20of%20the%20Graphics%20class%20in%20Java?",answer:"To%20perform%20drawing%20operations%20on%20components"},{question:"What%20is%20the%20starting%20point%20of%20the%20coordinate%20system%20in%20Java's%20Graphics%20class?",answer:"Top-left%20corner%20of%20the%20component"},{question:"How%20can%20you%20set%20the%20color%20used%20for%20drawing%20in%20the%20Graphics%20class?",answer:"By%20calling%20the%20setColor()%20method%20with%20a%20Color%20object"},{question:"What%20is%20the%20primary%20advantage%20of%20using%20the%20Graphics2D%20class%20over%20the%20Graphics%20class?",answer:"It%20provides%20methods%20for%20advanced%20graphics%20operations%20such%20as%20transformations%20and%20anti-aliasing."},{question:"What%20does%20the%20drawLine()%20method%20in%20the%20Graphics%20class%20do?",answer:"Draws%20a%20line%20between%20two%20specified%20points"},{question:"What%20is%20the%20role%20of%20the%20paintComponent()%20method%20in%20Java%20Swing?",answer:"To%20draw%20custom%20graphics%20on%20a%20component"},{question:"How%20can%20you%20draw%20a%20filled%20rectangle%20using%20the%20Graphics%20class?",answer:"Use%20the%20fillRect()%20method"},{question:"How%20can%20you%20clear%20the%20drawing%20area%20in%20a%20Java%20Swing%20component?",answer:"Fill%20the%20area%20with%20the%20background%20color%20using%20fillRect()"},{question:"Which%20method%20in%20the%20Graphics%20class%20is%20used%20to%20draw%20an%20arc?",answer:"drawArc()"},{question:"How%20can%20you%20create%20smooth%20edges%20on%20shapes%20in%20Java%20graphics?",answer:"Use%20the%20setRenderingHint()%20method%20with%20anti-aliasing%20enabled"},{question:"How%20can%20you%20rotate%20a%20shape%20using%20the%20Graphics2D%20class?",answer:"Use%20the%20rotate()%20method%20to%20specify%20the%20rotation%20angle"},{question:"Which%20of%20the%20following%20statements%20is%20true%20about%20custom%20painting%20in%20Java?",answer:"The%20paintComponent()%20method%20is%20used%20to%20customize%20how%20a%20component%20is%20rendered."},{question:"What%20does%20the%20setColor()%20method%20in%20the%20Graphics%20class%20do?",answer:"Specifies%20the%20color%20used%20for%20subsequent%20drawing%20operations"},{question:"How%20do%20you%20draw%20text%20on%20a%20component%20using%20the%20Graphics%20class?",answer:"Call%20the%20drawString()%20method%20with%20the%20text%20and%20coordinates"},{question:"Which%20method%20would%20you%20use%20to%20draw%20a%20filled%20shape?",answer:"fillRect(),%20fillOval(),%20or%20fillPolygon()"},{question:"What%20is%20the%20purpose%20of%20the%20fillRect()%20method%20in%20Java's%20Graphics%20class?",answer:"To%20draw%20and%20fill%20a%20rectangle%20with%20the%20current%20color"},{question:"How%20do%20you%20draw%20a%20square%20using%20the%20drawRect()%20method%20in%20Java?",answer:"Specify%20equal%20width%20and%20height%20for%20the%20rectangle"},{question:"What%20is%20the%20function%20of%20the%20setColor()%20method%20in%20the%20Graphics%20class?",answer:"To%20set%20the%20color%20used%20for%20subsequent%20drawing%20operations"},{question:"Which%20parameter%20is%20NOT%20required%20for%20the%20drawRect()%20method?",answer:"Color"},{question:"Which%20method%20is%20used%20to%20draw%20a%20filled%20circle%20in%20Java?",answer:"fillOval()"},{question:"How%20can%20you%20draw%20a%20triangle%20in%20Java?",answer:"Use%20the%20drawPolygon()%20method%20with%20three%20coordinate%20points"},{question:"What%20does%20the%20drawOval()%20method%20do%20in%20Java?",answer:"Draws%20the%20outline%20of%20an%20oval%20within%20a%20specified%20bounding%20rectangle"},{question:"How%20can%20you%20draw%20a%20regular%20polygon,%20such%20as%20a%20hexagon,%20using%20Java's%20Graphics%20class?",answer:"Use%20the%20drawPolygon()%20method%20with%20an%20array%20of%20x%20and%20y%20coordinates"},{question:"What%20does%20the%20drawLine()%20method%20in%20Java%20do?",answer:"Draws%20a%20straight%20line%20between%20two%20specified%20points"},{question:"Which%20of%20the%20following%20methods%20would%20you%20use%20to%20draw%20text%20on%20a%20component?",answer:"drawString()"},{question:"What%20is%20the%20purpose%20of%20the%20fillRect()%20method?",answer:"To%20fill%20a%20rectangular%20area%20with%20the%20current%20drawing%20color"},{question:"What%20is%20required%20to%20draw%20a%20triangle%20using%20Java's%20Graphics%20class?",answer:"Use%20the%20drawPolygon()%20method%20with%20three%20points"},{question:"What%20must%20be%20true%20for%20the%20drawOval()%20method%20to%20draw%20a%20perfect%20circle?",answer:"The%20bounding%20rectangle's%20width%20and%20height%20must%20be%20equal"},{question:"What%20happens%20when%20you%20use%20the%20fillPolygon()%20method%20with%20an%20array%20of%20points?",answer:"A%20filled%20shape%20is%20created%20based%20on%20the%20specified%20points"},{question:"Which%20method%20allows%20you%20to%20draw%20connected%20lines%20to%20form%20a%20closed%20shape?",answer:"drawPolygon()"},{question:"Which%20method%20would%20you%20use%20to%20draw%20a%20filled%20rectangle?",answer:"fillRect()"},{question:"How%20can%20you%20draw%20a%20square%20using%20Java's%20Graphics%20class?",answer:"Use%20the%20fillRect()%20method%20with%20equal%20width%20and%20height"},{question:"How%20can%20you%20set%20the%20color%20used%20for%20drawing%20shapes?",answer:"Use%20the%20setColor()%20method%20with%20a%20Color%20object"},{question:"What%20does%20the%20drawLine()%20method%20do%20in%20Java?",answer:"Draws%20a%20line%20between%20two%20specified%20points"},{question:"What%20does%20the%20drawArc()%20method%20require%20to%20draw%20a%20partial%20circle?",answer:"Width,%20height,%20and%20the%20number%20of%20degrees%20for%20the%20arc"},{question:"What%20does%20the%20drawRoundRect()%20method%20do?",answer:"Draws%20a%20rectangle%20with%20rounded%20corners"},{question:"Which%20method%20would%20you%20use%20to%20set%20the%20current%20drawing%20color%20in%20Java?",answer:"setColor()"},{question:"What%20is%20the%20difference%20between%20drawOval()%20and%20fillOval()%20in%20Java?",answer:"drawOval()%20draws%20the%20outline,%20while%20fillOval()%20fills%20the%20oval%20with%20color"},{question:"How%20do%20you%20ensure%20a%20shape%20is%20redrawn%20correctly%20when%20the%20window%20is%20resized?",answer:"Override%20the%20paintComponent()%20method"},{question:"Which%20method%20would%20you%20use%20to%20draw%20a%20filled%20triangle?",answer:"fillPolygon()"},{question:"What%20happens%20if%20you%20call%20the%20setColor()%20method%20before%20drawing%20a%20shape?",answer:"The%20shape%20is%20drawn%20with%20the%20specified%20color"},{question:"How%20can%20you%20create%20a%20filled%20shape%20with%20any%20number%20of%20sides?",answer:"Use%20the%20fillPolygon()%20method%20with%20an%20array%20of%20x%20and%20y%20coordinates"},{question:"How%20can%20you%20change%20the%20appearance%20of%20a%20shape's%20edges%20to%20be%20smoother?",answer:"Enable%20anti-aliasing%20using%20the%20Graphics2D%20class"},{question:"How%20can%20you%20draw%20a%20regular%20hexagon%20in%20Java?",answer:"Use%20the%20drawPolygon()%20method%20with%20six%20coordinate%20points"},{question:"How%20do%20you%20ensure%20that%20the%20drawn%20shapes%20are%20updated%20correctly%20when%20the%20window%20is%20resized?",answer:"Use%20the%20paintComponent()%20method%20and%20call%20super.paintComponent(g)"},{question:"What%20is%20the%20effect%20of%20calling%20fillPolygon()%20in%20the%20Graphics%20class?",answer:"It%20fills%20a%20polygon%20with%20the%20current%20drawing%20color"},{question:"What%20does%20the%20drawPolygon()%20method%20do%20in%20Java?",answer:"Draws%20a%20series%20of%20connected%20lines%20to%20form%20a%20closed%20shape"},{question:"How%20can%20you%20draw%20a%20rectangle%20with%20rounded%20corners%20in%20Java?",answer:"Use%20the%20drawRoundRect()%20method"},{question:"How%20can%20you%20draw%20multiple%20connected%20lines%20to%20create%20a%20complex%20shape?",answer:"Use%20the%20drawPolygon()%20method"},{question:"How%20can%20you%20draw%20a%20shape%20with%20a%20gradient%20color%20in%20Java?",answer:"Use%20the%20Graphics2D%20class%20with%20GradientPaint"},{question:"Which%20method%20is%20used%20to%20draw%20a%20filled%20oval?",answer:"fillOval()"},{question:"What%20does%20the%20drawArc()%20method%20do%20in%20Java?",answer:"Draws%20an%20arc%20of%20an%20ellipse%20defined%20by%20a%20bounding%20rectangle"},{question:"How%20do%20you%20draw%20a%20filled%20square%20using%20Java's%20Graphics%20class?",answer:"Use%20the%20fillRect()%20method%20with%20equal%20width%20and%20height"},{question:"How%20can%20you%20set%20the%20current%20color%20for%20drawing%20shapes%20in%20Java?",answer:"Call%20the%20setColor()%20method%20with%20a%20Color%20object"},{question:"What%20is%20the%20result%20of%20calling%20the%20drawRect()%20method%20in%20the%20Graphics%20class?",answer:"It%20draws%20the%20outline%20of%20a%20rectangle."},{question:"What%20is%20the%20main%20function%20of%20the%20Graphics%20class%20in%20Java?",answer:"Creating%20and%20drawing%20graphics%20on%20components"},{question:"What%20happens%20if%20you%20call%20super.paintComponent(g)%20in%20a%20custom%20paintComponent()%20method?",answer:"It%20clears%20the%20drawing%20area%20before%20custom%20painting."},{question:"How%20can%20you%20change%20the%20drawing%20color%20in%20Java's%20Graphics%20class?",answer:"Use%20the%20setColor()%20method%20with%20a%20Color%20object."},{question:"How%20do%20you%20perform%20custom%20painting%20in%20Java%20Swing?",answer:"Override%20the%20paintComponent()%20method%20of%20JPanel"},{question:"What%20does%20the%20setRenderingHint()%20method%20in%20Graphics2D%20do?",answer:"It%20enables%20features%20such%20as%20anti-aliasing%20and%20text%20smoothing."},{question:"Which%20method%20in%20Graphics%20is%20used%20to%20draw%20text?",answer:"drawString()"},{question:"What%20is%20the%20coordinate%20origin%20in%20Java's%20Graphics%20class?",answer:"Top-left%20corner%20of%20the%20component"},{question:"How%20can%20you%20add%20smooth%20edges%20to%20drawn%20shapes%20in%20Java?",answer:"Enable%20anti-aliasing%20using%20the%20Graphics2D%20class"},{question:"How%20do%20you%20set%20the%20font%20for%20drawing%20text%20in%20Java's%20Graphics%20class?",answer:"Use%20the%20setFont()%20method"},{question:"What%20is%20the%20difference%20between%20drawRect()%20and%20fillRect()%20methods%20in%20Java?",answer:"drawRect()%20draws%20the%20border,%20while%20fillRect()%20fills%20the%20rectangle%20with%20color."},{question:"Which%20of%20the%20following%20is%20NOT%20a%20valid%20method%20in%20the%20Graphics%20class?",answer:"drawRectangle()"},{question:"Which%20method%20would%20you%20use%20to%20draw%20a%20line%20between%20two%20points?",answer:"drawLine()"},{question:"What%20does%20overriding%20the%20paintComponent()%20method%20in%20a%20JPanel%20allow%20you%20to%20do?",answer:"Customize%20the%20drawing%20of%20the%20component"},{question:"What%20does%20anti-aliasing%20do%20in%20computer%20graphics?",answer:"It%20improves%20the%20quality%20of%20images%20by%20smoothing%20jagged%20edges."},{question:"How%20can%20you%20ensure%20that%20custom%20painting%20is%20updated%20correctly%20when%20a%20component%20is%20resized?",answer:"Use%20the%20paintComponent()%20method%20and%20call%20super.paintComponent(g)"},{question:"What%20is%20the%20purpose%20of%20the%20fillOval()%20method%20in%20Java?",answer:"To%20fill%20the%20oval%20with%20the%20current%20drawing%20color"},{question:"How%20can%20you%20rotate%20a%20shape%20using%20the%20Graphics2D%20class?",answer:"Use%20the%20rotate()%20method%20with%20an%20angle%20value"},{question:"What%20happens%20when%20you%20call%20repaint()%20on%20a%20Java%20component?",answer:"The%20component's%20paintComponent()%20method%20is%20called%20to%20redraw%20it."},{question:"How%20can%20you%20draw%20a%20circle%20using%20the%20drawOval()%20method?",answer:"Use%20equal%20width%20and%20height%20for%20the%20bounding%20rectangle."}];questionsAndAnswers.forEach(qa%20=>%20{const%20questionElem=Array.from(document.querySelectorAll(".qtext")).find(el%20=>%20el.textContent.includes(qa.question));if(questionElem){const%20answerElem=Array.from(questionElem.parentNode.querySelectorAll("input[type=radio]")).find(input%20=>%20input.nextElementSibling.textContent.includes(qa.answer));if(answerElem){answerElem.click();actionPerformed=true}}});const%20nextNav=document.getElementById('mod_quiz-next-nav');if(nextNav){nextNav.click();actionPerformed=true}if(!actionPerformed){var%20element=document.getElementById('next-activity-link');if(element){element.click()}%20else%20{alert("Element%20not%20found!")}}})();
